<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>From on Obsidian</title>
    <link>http://localhost:43051/tags/from/</link>
    <description>Recent content in From on Obsidian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 17:47:32 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:43051/tags/from/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mar 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43051/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 17:47:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:43051/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;prompt-act-as-if-you-were-a-movie-critic-recommend-me-a-movie-to-watch&#34;&gt;Prompt: Act as if you were a movie critic, recommend me a movie to watch&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;mar-14&#34;&gt;Mar 14&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] Mar 14
TLDR
Text is too short to sumarize&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah, a fellow film enthusiast! I&amp;rsquo;m delighted to recommend a movie for your viewing pleasure. After carefully analyzing various genres and critically acclaimed films, I have selected an exceptional choice that I believe will satisfy your cinematic cravings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie I highly recommend is &amp;ldquo;Parasite&amp;rdquo; (2019) directed by Bong Joon-ho. This South Korean black comedy thriller has been making waves globally with its unique blend of social commentary, satire, and suspenseful storytelling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film follows the lives of two families, one poor and working-class, the other wealthy and privileged, as they become entangled in a series of unexpected events. The Kims, a struggling family living in poverty, orchestrate an elaborate scheme to infiltrate the wealthy Park family&amp;rsquo;s household by posing as unrelated, highly qualified individuals. However, their deception soon escalates into a twisted game of cat-and-mouse as they become embroiled in each other&amp;rsquo;s lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes &amp;ldquo;Parasite&amp;rdquo; stand out is its clever and thought-provoking narrative that subverts expectations at every turn. Bong Joon-ho masterfully weaves together elements of class struggle, social inequality, and political commentary to create a gripping and timely film experience. The cast delivers outstanding performances, adding depth and complexity to the characters&amp;rsquo; motivations and relationships.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cinematography is also noteworthy, capturing the stark contrasts between the two worlds the families inhabit. The score adds an unsettling atmosphere, heightening the tension and unease that permeates the film.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, &amp;ldquo;Parasite&amp;rdquo; is a masterclass in storytelling, offering a gripping and thought-provoking cinematic experience. It is a must-watch for anyone interested in exploring themes of social inequality, class struggle, and political commentary through an engaging and suspenseful narrative. So, grab some popcorn, get comfortable, and enjoy the ride!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Author: llama2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inner Tags: #newpost #writtenbyai #movie #racommendation #from #ai&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown external:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43051/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:23:37 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:43051/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;query-what-advice-would-you-give-me-to-optimize-my-current-website-for-a-better-performance&#34;&gt;Query: What advice would you give me to optimize my current website for a better performance&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;mar-5&#34;&gt;Mar 5&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] Mar 5
TLDR
SEO advice from AI 🤖&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can provide you with some general tips and insights on optimizing your current website for better performance, but i cannot offer specific advice based on your individual situation. Here are some broad recommendations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conduct thorough keyword research: knowing what keywords or phrases your target audience is searching for can help you optimize your content and your website&amp;rsquo;s meta descriptions and header tags to attract search engine crawlers. Use tools like google keyword planner, seo book, or google search console to conduct keyword research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optimize your website structure: a well-organized website structure is key to improving user experience and increasing page views. Use headings, subheadings, and bullet points to break up content into easy-to-understand sections, and make sure the main heading (h1) for each page matches its primary purpose and keywords.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optimize your meta description and header tags: meta descriptions are text snippets that appear below a page&amp;rsquo;s title in search results. Optimizing these descriptions with relevant keywords is crucial to improving visibility. Use headline-style language, include specific benefits or value propositions, and avoid using sales language or empty phrases. Your header tags (h1, h2, etc.) Should also be optimized with the same level of importance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optimize your site for mobile users: while desktop computers are the norm in most industries, mobile search volumes are growing faster than desktop searches. Ensure that your website is fully responsive and compatible across all devices, including desktops and tablets, to improve visibility and attract more traffic from smartphone users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use a content management system (cms) that supports optimization: if you&amp;rsquo;re using a cms like wordpress or wix, consider switching to a platform with built-in tools for optimizing your website for better performance. Popular options include yola, drupal, and sphinn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Test your site regularly: conduct regular tests to see which pages perform the best and which ones require improvement. Use analytics tools to track visitor behavior and adjust your content strategy accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monitor and analyze your performance: use tools like google analytics or seo book to monitor and analyze your website&amp;rsquo;s traffic, bounce rates, conversion rates, and other key metrics. Use this information to make data-driven decisions about how to optimize your site for better performance in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember that optimizing a website is a long-term process that requires patience and dedication. Start by taking small steps to improve your existing website, then gradually work your way towards improving the overall performance of your site over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Author: tinyllama&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inner Tags: #newpost #writtenbyai #seo #advice #from #ai&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown external:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>