<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2022 on Obsidian notes</title>
    <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/tags/2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2022 on Obsidian notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All rights belong to artefaktas.eu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:33 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/tags/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jul 17</title>
      <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2022-07/jul-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:33 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2022-07/jul-17/</guid>
      <description>Jul 17 [!tldr] Jul 17 Did not read again? This is a shor post about how I use the information I find to create some of my blog posts.
Some of you might be interested in the information I use in writing my newest blog posts. I can tell you one thing. I use multiple sources from different places all around the internet and even some of my old notebooks.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;jul-17&#34;&gt;Jul 17&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] Jul 17
Did not read again? This is a shor post about how I use the information I find to create some of my blog posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of you might be interested in the information I use in writing my newest blog posts. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can tell you one thing. I use multiple sources from different places all around the internet and even some of my old notebooks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Almost every time I need to write something about the code or tools I use, I read lots of documentation and test a few things before writing. I want to make correct assumptions based on my personal experience, so that is why I investigate a bunch of functionalities myself. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is helpful when you want to write some lengthy technical texts, but what about something else?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would it be possible to use any of the TikTok videos as a base material for a start? Well, of course, it would. Though, you would need to view the material as sceptically as possible. Not everything you find on the internet is the truth. You may need to make the conclusions yourselves. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So my recipe is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch the video.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify which parts of it are accurate and which are not.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recheck the information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read some documentation or research papers if it is possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is there a chance that you could test the theory? Test it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write down your conclusions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write your post and publish it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exists:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jul 16</title>
      <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2022-07/jul-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 14:19:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2022-07/jul-16/</guid>
      <description>Jul 16 [!tldr] Jul 16 Just another post. This one is about the best blogging system around. To sum up, it does not exist.
Is there a perfect content management system for blogging? I still doubt it.
You see, I tried almost every possible tool that I could find all over the internet.
Joomla, WordPress, Jekyll, Hugo, Blogger - you name it. I even constructed a blogging tool myself a long time ago to prove that it is possible to usae almost any web tool you like to create a website you will enjoy using.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;jul-16&#34;&gt;Jul 16&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] Jul 16
Just another post. This one is about the best blogging system around. To sum up, it does not exist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is there a perfect content management system for blogging? I still doubt it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You see, I tried almost every possible tool that I could find all over the internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joomla, WordPress, Jekyll, Hugo, Blogger - you name it. I even constructed a blogging tool myself a long time ago to prove that it is possible to usae almost any web tool you like to create a website you will enjoy using. Well, as long as it is formatted in a suitable manner according to WEB guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few important key points are only valid HTML structure, well-formatted RSS feed, easy-to-use graphical user interface, safety and appealing looks to your visitors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do you differ a good CMS from a bad one? How should you choose the one you trully need? I think you need some more information to decide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;let-us-talk-about-flat-file-content-management-systems&#34;&gt;Let us talk about Flat File Content Management Systems&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is a &amp;ldquo;Flat File CMS&amp;rdquo;? What is a website generator? Could you tell me? I am sure that I can provide you with some information about those thingies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;flat-file-cms&#34;&gt;Flat File CMS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How does a system like that even works? Hm, that is not as complicated, as you might think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First things first, a flat file content management system is able to store and edit files. The main important thing is that such a system does not use a database atll. It stores data in the files and use them to generate webpages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second, most of the Flat file Systems have an admin panel to manage all of the recordings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A perfect example of a FFCMS could be Grav: &lt;a href=&#34;https://getgrav.org/&#34;&gt;https://getgrav.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advantages:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast building times&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Admin panel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple users support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;website-generators&#34;&gt;Website generators&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website generators are sets of specific tools dedicated to generate websites. Simple as that. Website generators can use almost any text files, such as JSON, markdown, html, text or even something else. One of the drawbacks of using such systems could be a lack of editing tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, there are plenty of text editing tools you could find online or on your computer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Typora&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gedit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kchem&amp;hellip; Notepad&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obsidian&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sublime Text&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual Studio Code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Almost any code or text editor should do the job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main difference between WG and FFCMS is that in order to publish your work, you will have to write some basic commands into the command line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let us use some imagination. Here are two steps after you finish writing your breathtaking blog post:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hugo (Builds/Rebuilds your project)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;firebase deploy (Puts the files of public directory into a firebase)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some website generator examples:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hugo (&lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;https://gohugo.io/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jekyll (&lt;a href=&#34;https://jekyllrb.com/&#34;&gt;https://jekyllrb.com/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gatsby (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gatsbyjs.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.gatsbyjs.com/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advantages:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast building times !&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The freedom to create templates by yourselves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drawbacks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Almost everytime you need to include an extra functionality into your pages you will have to &amp;ldquo;google around&amp;rdquo; the solutions yourselves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building configuration&amp;hellip; You will have to put your hands into the dirt sooner or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lack of editing tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;blogger-wordpress-joomla-and-other-similar-products&#34;&gt;Blogger, Wordpress, Joomla and other similar products&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, could you tell me how these ones differ from FFCMS or a simple website generator? In case you could not, I can assure you that it is particulary easy to grasp the basic concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each one of the mentioned CMS use SQL databases to store the information. They use a special programmed steps to get this information on command (press of a button) and build the pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advantages:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The functionality can be improved by installing various plugins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple user support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drawbacks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They tend to be a bit slow sometimes depending on your service provider and use-case scenarios&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They tend to have some bugggggggs and security holes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite all of those things I mentioned above, the overall approach to create a stylish website depends totally on the user and the knowledge of tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can make a perfect website with almost every content management system or generator. I admit that the most straightforward solution for a novice could be Wordpress or Blogger. In some cases, when a person has a bit more understanding how to operate computer systems, there is nothing that could not be done with a generator and some extra effort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I could give you an advice, here it is. If you are a novice user, just choose the best option based on your personal knowledge and watch a few youtube videos to make the final decision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personally, I do not think that there is a perfect tool around to solve all of your WEB issues. Web standards change frequently, so you might need to modify a couple of things here and there later. Choose wisely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exists:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jul 15</title>
      <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2022-07/jul-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 18:58:39 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2022-07/jul-15/</guid>
      <description>Jul 15 [!tldr] Jul 15 There is nothing to read yet. This is a test post.
Testing my new toolkit I guess I made something fascinating today. I mixed a couple of well-known technologies and here we are.
Everytime I run a shell command to sync latest posts, with the help of Hugo, Github and Cloudflare pages, new posts appear online with almost no effort.
[!hint] Hint
#!/bin/bash CURRENTDATE=`date +&amp;#34;%Y-%m-%d %T&amp;#34;` hugo git add * -f message=&amp;#34;Obsidian update: &amp;#34;$CURRENTDATE git commit -m &amp;#34;$message&amp;#34; git push Final solution If you want to replicate this</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;jul-15&#34;&gt;Jul 15&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] Jul 15
There is nothing to read yet. This is a test post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;testing-my-new-toolkit&#34;&gt;Testing my new toolkit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I made something fascinating today. I mixed a couple of well-known technologies and here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everytime I run a shell command to sync latest posts, with the help of Hugo, Github and Cloudflare pages, new posts appear online with almost no effort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!hint] Hint&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;#!/bin/bash

CURRENTDATE=`date +&amp;#34;%Y-%m-%d %T&amp;#34;`

hugo

git add * -f

message=&amp;#34;Obsidian update: &amp;#34;$CURRENTDATE

git commit -m &amp;#34;$message&amp;#34;

git push
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;final-solution&#34;&gt;Final solution&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to replicate this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create a file called remote.sh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insert this code inside&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;
#!/bin/bash

CURRENTDATE=`date +&amp;#34;%Y-%m-%d %T&amp;#34;`

git add content -f

git add public -f

message=&amp;#34;Obsidian update: &amp;#34;$CURRENTDATE

git commit -m &amp;#34;$message&amp;#34;

git push
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create a good-named alias in your ~/.bashrc file&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;
alias obsidianbuild=&amp;#34;cd /home/yourusername/Desktop/vaults/interconnection/ &amp;amp;&amp;amp; hugo &amp;amp;&amp;amp; ./remote.sh&amp;#34;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source your ~/.bashrc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;
source ~/.bashrc
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;open-your-terminal&#34;&gt;Open your terminal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And run a command&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;
obsidianbuild
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanban Board</title>
      <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/kanban/kanban-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 13:58:39 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/kanban/kanban-board/</guid>
      <description>Preparing Doing Add more posts Done Test rebuilds ! Archive Complete
%% kanban:settings
{&amp;#34;kanban-plugin&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;basic&amp;#34;} %%</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;preparing&#34;&gt;Preparing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doing&#34;&gt;Doing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Add more posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;done&#34;&gt;Done&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Test rebuilds !&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;archive&#34;&gt;Archive&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Complete&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;%% kanban:settings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&amp;#34;kanban-plugin&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;basic&amp;#34;}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;%%&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
