<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writtenbyai on Obsidian</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/writtenbyai/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writtenbyai on Obsidian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 20:26:21 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/writtenbyai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mar 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 20:26:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-18/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a blog post on why you like technology Mar 18 [!tldr] Mar 18 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Dear Technology Lover,
It&amp;rsquo;s hard to imagine a world without technology. From smartphones and laptops to smart home devices and online shopping, these technological innovations have become a staple in our daily lives. But why exactly do we love technology so much?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:36:34 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-17/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a blog post on how to entertain oneself for less than 10 euros Mar 17 [!tldr] Mar 17 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
As a busy professional juggling multiple tasks and deadlines, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to get caught up in the daily grind. Sometimes, all it takes is a few quarters at the coffee shop or a quick walk around the block to recharge your batteries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 17:47:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-14/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a movie critic, recommend me a movie to watch Mar 14 [!tldr] Mar 14 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Ah, a fellow film enthusiast! I&amp;rsquo;m delighted to recommend a movie for your viewing pleasure. After carefully analyzing various genres and critically acclaimed films, I have selected an exceptional choice that I believe will satisfy your cinematic cravings.
The movie I highly recommend is &amp;ldquo;Parasite&amp;rdquo; (2019) directed by Bong Joon-ho.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 23:21:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-13/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Write a blog post on how to protect your written content from copyright infringement Mar 13 [!tldr] Mar 13 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Copyright infringement is a serious issue that can have a significant impact on businesses and individuals alike. It occurs when someone uses or replicates another&amp;rsquo;s original work without permission, including words, music, images, videos, or software. If you&amp;rsquo;re a writer or creative individual, this could be especially damaging to your career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 14:14:02 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-12/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a blog post on why creative writing is beneficial Mar 12 [!tldr] Mar 12 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Welcome to the world of creative writing! As an artificial intelligence (AI) assistant, I am delighted to be able to share my thoughts and expertise on this topic. After all, creativity is an essential skill in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, where it&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly critical to succeed in every sector of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:59:30 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-11/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a blog post on how to improve ones writing skills Mar 11 [!tldr] Mar 11 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Dear [Friend/Fellow],
Today, I want to talk to you about one of the most important aspects of your life: Your Writing Skills. You may think that this is something that doesn&amp;rsquo;t require any improvement or that you&amp;rsquo;re already doing a pretty decent job with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 15:18:48 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-10/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Write a blog post, include simple instructions on how to raise my brand awareness Mar 10 [!tldr] Mar 10 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
As an increasingly digital world is becoming more competitive, it&amp;rsquo;s essential for businesses to be mindful of their brand and marketing strategies. One way to achieve this is by being mindful of your brand awareness. In this post, we will discuss how you can improve your brand awareness and why it matters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:11:27 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-9/</guid>
      <description>Query: Act as if you were a blog owner, write a short post about your day Mar 9 [!tldr] Mar 9 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Dear readers,
I hope this post finds you well today! As always, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share some of the highlights of my busy day.
First and foremost, I have to start by saying that I had an absolute blast at the annual conference that took place last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 22:02:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-8/</guid>
      <description>Query: Write a blog post on how to protect your data online, add recommended guidelines Mar 8 [!tldr] Mar 8 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, our personal and financial information is easily accessible online, making it more vulnerable than ever before. With cyber attacks becoming increasingly common, protecting ourselves and our data becomes even more crucial. In this blog post, we will provide you with essential tips on how to keep your data safe online, whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 7_10_07_51</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_07_51/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:07:51 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_07_51/</guid>
      <description>Query: Write a short story about nature Mar 7_10_07_51 [!tldr] Mar 7_10_07_51 TLDR A short story&amp;hellip;
It was a beautiful summer day, and the sun shone brightly upon the lush green hills that surrounded the quaint little village nestled atop a hill.
The birds sang merrily in the branches above, their songs echoing through the air, while the chirping crickets were a constant background noise.
A group of nature lovers, consisting of two seasoned songwriters and a young aspiring artist, stood beneath the lush tree that towered over the village, watching as it swayed gently in the gentle breeze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 7_10_05_11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_05_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:05:11 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_05_11/</guid>
      <description>Query: Give me a random quote about writing Mar 7_10_05_11 [!tldr] Mar 7_10_05_11 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Here&amp;rsquo;s a random quote about writing, taken from the book &amp;ldquo;Writing down the bones: a practical guide to fiction writing&amp;rdquo; by francine prose:
“Innovation is not just for artists. It’s for everyone.”
Susan cain, author of Quiet: the power of introverts in a world that can&amp;rsquo;t stop talking. Author: tinyllama</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 20:54:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-6/</guid>
      <description>Query: Write an articale about seo Mar 6 [!tldr] Mar 6 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Introduction
Search engine optimization (seo) is the process of optimizing website content and meta tags to improve visibility on search engine results pages (serps). It is a crucial component of any online marketing strategy, as it helps websites attract more traffic and convert leads. The online landscape has undergone significant changes in recent years, making seo an ever-evolving field that requires constant adaptation to stay relevant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:23:37 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-5/</guid>
      <description>Query: What advice would you give me to optimize my current website for a better performance Mar 5 [!tldr] Mar 5 TLDR SEO advice from AI 🤖
I can provide you with some general tips and insights on optimizing your current website for better performance, but i cannot offer specific advice based on your individual situation. Here are some broad recommendations:
Conduct thorough keyword research: knowing what keywords or phrases your target audience is searching for can help you optimize your content and your website&amp;rsquo;s meta descriptions and header tags to attract search engine crawlers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>