<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How on Obsidian</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/how/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How on Obsidian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 13:03:11 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/how/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mar 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 13:03:11 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-30/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Write a short guideline on how to cope with stress Mar 30 [!tldr] Mar 30 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Coping with stress is an important skill for maintaining mental well-being and overall health. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to help you manage stress effectively:
Identify the sources of stress in your life. This may involve keeping a journal to track when you experience high levels of stress and what events or situations seem to trigger it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:15:07 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-28/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Write a blog post on how to stay creative Mar 28 [!tldr] Mar 28 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, staying creative has become increasingly important. With all the distractions and interruptions, it can be challenging to find time for creativity in our busy schedules. But let me share with you a few tips on how to stay creative!
Take breaks: Sometimes we get so caught up in work or life that we forget to take breaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:14:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-26/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a developer, write a post on how to stay productive by using nowadays technologies Mar 26 [!tldr] Mar 26 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
As a busy programmer and project manager, I know how important it is to be efficient and focused to get things done. Here are some nowaday technologies that can help you stay productive:
Productivity software: There are several productivity software tools out there, such as Trello, Asana, Monday, and Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:59:30 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-11/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a blog post on how to improve ones writing skills Mar 11 [!tldr] Mar 11 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Dear [Friend/Fellow],
Today, I want to talk to you about one of the most important aspects of your life: Your Writing Skills. You may think that this is something that doesn&amp;rsquo;t require any improvement or that you&amp;rsquo;re already doing a pretty decent job with it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>