<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Written on Obsidian</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/written/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Written on Obsidian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 23:21:41 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/written/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mar 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 23:21:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-13/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;prompt-write-a-blog-post-on-how-to-protect-your-written-content-from-copyright-infringement&#34;&gt;Prompt: Write a blog post on how to protect your written content from copyright infringement&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;mar-13&#34;&gt;Mar 13&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] Mar 13
TLDR
Text is too short to sumarize&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright infringement is a serious issue that can have a significant impact on businesses and individuals alike. It occurs when someone uses or replicates another&amp;rsquo;s original work without permission, including words, music, images, videos, or software. If you&amp;rsquo;re a writer or creative individual, this could be especially damaging to your career.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some ways to protect your written content from copyright infraction:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t share your ideas with anyone else: Before sharing your work with anyone else, make sure they have permission to use it. If you create a piece of content on behalf of your business or organization, ask the rights holder for permission beforehand. It&amp;rsquo;s also essential not to reuse content that has already been published elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure all sources are cited: When writing about something you found online, make sure to cite the original source so others can check their work and verify its validity. Also, ensure that the copied material is properly attributed to the original creator(s) in your document or article. This helps avoid copyright infringement while also giving credit where credit is due.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use Creative Commons Licenses: Creative Commons allows you to share your work under a license that grants others permission to use it. It&amp;rsquo;s important to read the license before using any content, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re not sure about its usage terms. When appropriate, consider using CC-BY or CC0 (Public Domain) licenses so that they can be used freely by anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay up to date with copyright laws: Make sure you know the current copyright law in your country, region, or industry. Keeping up with new legislation and adapting to it is essential for protecting your work from infringement. It can also help you avoid legal action and preserve your rights in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use a WordPress Plugin: There are several WordPress plugins that help protect your content. The Free Content ID plugin allows you to add a &amp;ldquo;Free Content&amp;rdquo; tag to your posts or pages, while the Mega Content ID plugin also lets you use a free or premium WordPress theme with an added tag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, protecting your written content from copyright infraction is essential for maintaining it as valuable and original work. By taking these precautions, you can ensure that you keep your intellectual property safe while still allowing others to publish their ideas effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Author: tinyllama&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inner Tags: #newpost #writtenbyai #written #content #protecting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown external:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 7_10_07_51</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_07_51/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:07:51 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_07_51/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;query-write-a-short-story-about-nature&#34;&gt;Query: Write a short story about nature&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;mar-7_10_07_51&#34;&gt;Mar 7_10_07_51&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] Mar 7_10_07_51
TLDR
A short story&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a beautiful summer day, and the sun shone brightly upon the lush green hills that surrounded the quaint little village nestled atop a hill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The birds sang merrily in the branches above, their songs echoing through the air, while the chirping crickets were a constant background noise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A group of nature lovers, consisting of two seasoned songwriters and a young aspiring artist, stood beneath the lush tree that towered over the village, watching as it swayed gently in the gentle breeze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The musician, a tall and imposing figure with a sharp nose and piercing green eyes, was deep in thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He had been sitting on a nearby bench for some time, composing a new song that would capture the essence of this beautiful environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he gazed upon the landscape around him, he noticed that something was missing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The air was still, the silence broken only by the occasional rustling leaves and distant bird chirps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He knew then that he had to sing about what he saw, hear what he heard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He took a deep breath, closed his eyes, and began to write.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His fingers moved over the piano keys in a rhythmic pattern, creating a melody that was both serene and captivating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The young artist, who sat nearby, listened intently, captivated by the song&amp;rsquo;s beauty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he continued to compose, the musician noticed something else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The air was filled with an unmistakable scent - a mixture of fresh grass, damp earth, and blooming flowers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was as if the air had been awakened from its slumber by the song&amp;rsquo;s melody, and it seemed to breathe life into the village once again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he finished his song, the musician took a deep breath and looked around him at the vibrant green landscape before him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He felt a sense of pride in his ability to capture this moment in time, and with that realization, he knew that this was what he had always been meant to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stood up from the bench and walked over to where the young artist was sitting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He approached her and began to play the song on the piano.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The musician could hear the young artist&amp;rsquo;s voice resonating with the melody, and he could see in her eyes that she was captivated by what he had created.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together they sang the song, the air around them filled with the sounds of nature&amp;rsquo;s harmony.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the sun began to set, they sat together, lost in the music, their words blending into one musical symphony.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As they exchanged glances and embraced, they knew that this was where they belonged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were a part of something bigger than themselves, and as they continued to sing the song for all to hear, they knew that they had found their calling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Author: tinyllama&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inner Tags: #newpost #writtenbyai #short #story #written #by #ai&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown external:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>