<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Written on Obsidian</title>
    <link>http://localhost:35907/tags/written/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Written on Obsidian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 23:21:41 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:35907/tags/written/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mar 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:35907/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 23:21:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:35907/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-13/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Write a blog post on how to protect your written content from copyright infringement Mar 13 [!tldr] Mar 13 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Copyright infringement is a serious issue that can have a significant impact on businesses and individuals alike. It occurs when someone uses or replicates another&amp;rsquo;s original work without permission, including words, music, images, videos, or software. If you&amp;rsquo;re a writer or creative individual, this could be especially damaging to your career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 7_10_07_51</title>
      <link>http://localhost:35907/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_07_51/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:07:51 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:35907/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_07_51/</guid>
      <description>Query: Write a short story about nature Mar 7_10_07_51 [!tldr] Mar 7_10_07_51 TLDR A short story&amp;hellip;
It was a beautiful summer day, and the sun shone brightly upon the lush green hills that surrounded the quaint little village nestled atop a hill.
The birds sang merrily in the branches above, their songs echoing through the air, while the chirping crickets were a constant background noise.
A group of nature lovers, consisting of two seasoned songwriters and a young aspiring artist, stood beneath the lush tree that towered over the village, watching as it swayed gently in the gentle breeze.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>