<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newpost on Obsidian notes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/newpost/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newpost on Obsidian notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:59:30 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/newpost/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mar 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:59:30 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-11/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a blog post on how to improve ones writing skills Mar 11 [!tldr] Mar 11 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Dear [Friend/Fellow],
Today, I want to talk to you about one of the most important aspects of your life: Your Writing Skills. You may think that this is something that doesn&amp;rsquo;t require any improvement or that you&amp;rsquo;re already doing a pretty decent job with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 15:18:48 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-10/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Write a blog post, include simple instructions on how to raise my brand awareness Mar 10 [!tldr] Mar 10 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
As an increasingly digital world is becoming more competitive, it&amp;rsquo;s essential for businesses to be mindful of their brand and marketing strategies. One way to achieve this is by being mindful of your brand awareness. In this post, we will discuss how you can improve your brand awareness and why it matters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:11:27 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-9/</guid>
      <description>Query: Act as if you were a blog owner, write a short post about your day Mar 9 [!tldr] Mar 9 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Dear readers,
I hope this post finds you well today! As always, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share some of the highlights of my busy day.
First and foremost, I have to start by saying that I had an absolute blast at the annual conference that took place last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 22:02:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-8/</guid>
      <description>Query: Write a blog post on how to protect your data online, add recommended guidelines Mar 8 [!tldr] Mar 8 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, our personal and financial information is easily accessible online, making it more vulnerable than ever before. With cyber attacks becoming increasingly common, protecting ourselves and our data becomes even more crucial. In this blog post, we will provide you with essential tips on how to keep your data safe online, whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 7_10_07_51</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_07_51/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:07:51 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_07_51/</guid>
      <description>Query: Write a short story about nature Mar 7_10_07_51 [!tldr] Mar 7_10_07_51 TLDR A short story&amp;hellip;
It was a beautiful summer day, and the sun shone brightly upon the lush green hills that surrounded the quaint little village nestled atop a hill.
The birds sang merrily in the branches above, their songs echoing through the air, while the chirping crickets were a constant background noise.
A group of nature lovers, consisting of two seasoned songwriters and a young aspiring artist, stood beneath the lush tree that towered over the village, watching as it swayed gently in the gentle breeze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 7_10_05_11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_05_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:05:11 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7_10_05_11/</guid>
      <description>Query: Give me a random quote about writing Mar 7_10_05_11 [!tldr] Mar 7_10_05_11 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Here&amp;rsquo;s a random quote about writing, taken from the book &amp;ldquo;Writing down the bones: a practical guide to fiction writing&amp;rdquo; by francine prose:
“Innovation is not just for artists. It’s for everyone.”
Susan cain, author of Quiet: the power of introverts in a world that can&amp;rsquo;t stop talking. Author: tinyllama</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:28:39 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-7/</guid>
      <description>Query: Get a random quote about writing Mar 7 [!tldr] Mar 7 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
&amp;ldquo;Writing is one of the most beautiful and transformative crafts we all know. It&amp;rsquo;s like a painter who paints with words, to create a canvas that speaks on its own. As I sit here, lost in my thoughts, writing this, i feel a sense of euphoria that i haven&amp;rsquo;t felt in some time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 20:54:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-6/</guid>
      <description>Query: Write an articale about seo Mar 6 [!tldr] Mar 6 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Introduction
Search engine optimization (seo) is the process of optimizing website content and meta tags to improve visibility on search engine results pages (serps). It is a crucial component of any online marketing strategy, as it helps websites attract more traffic and convert leads. The online landscape has undergone significant changes in recent years, making seo an ever-evolving field that requires constant adaptation to stay relevant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:23:37 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-5/</guid>
      <description>Query: What advice would you give me to optimize my current website for a better performance Mar 5 [!tldr] Mar 5 TLDR SEO advice from AI 🤖
I can provide you with some general tips and insights on optimizing your current website for better performance, but i cannot offer specific advice based on your individual situation. Here are some broad recommendations:
Conduct thorough keyword research: knowing what keywords or phrases your target audience is searching for can help you optimize your content and your website&amp;rsquo;s meta descriptions and header tags to attract search engine crawlers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 16:05:36 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-4/</guid>
      <description>Mar 4 [!tldr] Mar 4 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
In the woods, amidst the trees, where shadows dance and the leaves sway, a gentle breeze whispers softly, as leaves whisper secrets they keep.
Wildflowers bloom in the springtime, and the air is filled with song, the rustling of leaves, and the hum of bees, all blend together in a symphony.
A bird sings, in a sweet melody, as birdsong echoes through the night, a symphony of sounds that never cease, in this tranquil forest, where they&amp;rsquo;re free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:33:27 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-3/</guid>
      <description>Mar 3 [!tldr] Mar 3 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
In the year 2050, artificial intelligence (ai) had already reached a level of advanced technological sophistication that surpassed human intelligence. Humans now relied on ais to do almost everything from driving cars to running complex business operations. However, the relationship between humans and ais was not always harmonious. In a crowded public transportation system in the city of New York, a group of commuters were caught in an unexpected traffic jam due to an ai-powered transportation control system that had malfunctioned.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>