<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Good on Obsidian</title>
    <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/tags/good/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Good on Obsidian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:19:33 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/tags/good/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>May 10_19_19_33</title>
      <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2024-05/may-10_19_19_33/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:19:33 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2024-05/may-10_19_19_33/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;query-write-a-short-tutorial-on-how-to-create-a-great-blog-post-do-not-use-numbering&#34;&gt;Query: Write a short tutorial on how to create a great blog post, do not use numbering&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;may-10_19_19_33&#34;&gt;May 10_19_19_33&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] May 10_19_19_33
TLDR
Text is too short to sumarize&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Certainly! Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide for creating a great blog post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;define-your-goals-and-target-audience-before-you-start-writing-your-blog-post-you-need-to-define-what-you-want-to-achieve-with-it&#34;&gt;Define your goals and target audience: before you start writing your blog post, you need to define what you want to achieve with it.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you trying to increase website traffic?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attain a new client base?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gain more followers on social media?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you have a clear idea of your goals, the rest of the process becomes easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;brainstorm-ideas-create-a-list-of-topics-that-relate-to-your-goals-and-target-audience&#34;&gt;Brainstorm ideas: create a list of topics that relate to your goals and target audience.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use online tools like google sheets or trello to organize your ideas and prioritize them accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about your topic in detail and what you want to say in the blog post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;choose-your-writing-style-depending-on-your-goals-choose-a-writing-style-that-suits-your-audience&#34;&gt;Choose your writing style: depending on your goals, choose a writing style that suits your audience.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some popular writing styles include blogging, article writing, or newsletter copywriting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also try out different techniques like infographics and videos for a more engaging format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;select-your-content-once-youve-chosen-a-topic-select-the-content-that-will-best-support-your-goals-and-target-audience&#34;&gt;Select your content: once you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen a topic, select the content that will best support your goals and target audience.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some popular types of blog post include product reviews, industry news, tips and tricks, or how-to guides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;develop-your-idea-before-you-begin-writing-take-some-time-to-develop-your-idea&#34;&gt;Develop your idea: before you begin writing, take some time to develop your idea.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This means researching and gathering information about your topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t just copy-paste ideas from other blogs - instead, research the subject matter thoroughly and use your own unique perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;edit-your-post-once-you-have-a-rough-draft-its-time-to-edit-and-revise&#34;&gt;Edit your post: once you have a rough draft, it&amp;rsquo;s time to edit and revise.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pay attention to grammar and spelling errors, and make sure your language flows naturally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to proofread your post several times before submitting it for approval.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;optimize-your-post-finally-optimize-your-blog-post-for-search-engines-by-including-relevant-keywords-in-your-title-description-and-content&#34;&gt;Optimize your post: finally, optimize your blog post for search engines by including relevant keywords in your title, description, and content.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also use tools like google search console or semrush to track your blog&amp;rsquo;s performance and make adjustments as needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, creating a great blog post requires attention to detail, clear communication, and the ability to effectively convey information in a way that resonates with your audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With these steps in mind, you can write an engaging and informative blog post that will help you achieve your goals and attract new clients or customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Author: tinyllama:latest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inner Tags: #newpost #writtenbyai #ai #advice #on #how #to #create #a #good #blog #post&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown external:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 27</title>
      <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 11:47:04 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-27/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;prompt-act-as-if-you-were-a-writer-write-a-blog-post-on-how-to-create-good-titles-for-your-journal-entries&#34;&gt;Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a blog post on how to create good titles for your journal entries&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;mar-27&#34;&gt;Mar 27&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] Mar 27
TLDR
Text is too short to sumarize&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Title: The Art of Creating Captivating Journal Entries&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a writer, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to know that great titles are crucial for attracting and retaining readers. A well-crafted title not only captures the reader&amp;rsquo;s attention but also sets up expectations about what they can expect from your journal entries. In this blog post, we will explore the art of creating captivating journal entries by identifying and discussing some effective techniques for crafting engaging titles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start with a Punchline:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The title should immediately grab the reader&amp;rsquo;s attention and convey the main idea or theme of your entry. A catchy, memorable punchline is an excellent way to do this. For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;My Life in Monarchy: From Being Queen&amp;rsquo;s Handmaid to Queen&amp;rsquo;s Mistress&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This title immediately sets up the idea that the author has a unique perspective on the royal court system and is sharing their experiences as a member of the royal family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use Anecdotes or Personal Experiences:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using anecdotes, stories, or personal experiences can help you create a sense of intimacy and make your journal entries feel more relatable to readers. For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A Day in My Life as the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Mistress: From Cleaning Up Her Husband&amp;rsquo;s Messes to Raising His Children&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This title immediately sets up the idea that the author has a unique perspective on royal life and is sharing their experiences as a member of the royal family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use Quotations or Insights from Authoritative Sources:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using quotes or insights from authoritative sources can provide additional context and insight into your subject matter, making it more interesting to read. For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Royal Dilemma: My Life as the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Handmaid is a Nightmare&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This title immediately sets up the idea that the author has a unique perspective on royal life and is sharing their experiences as a member of the royal family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include Numbers or Statistics:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using statistics or numbers can make your entry more informative and interesting to read. For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;My Life in Monarchy: From Being Queen&amp;rsquo;s Handmaid to Queen&amp;rsquo;s Mistress, I Have Gone from Zero to One&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This title immediately sets up the idea that the author has a unique perspective on royal life and is sharing their experiences as a member of the royal family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use Metaphors or Similes:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using metaphors or similes can help create a poetic and descriptive language in your journal entries, making them more engaging to read. For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;My Life in Monarchy: From Being Queen&amp;rsquo;s Handmaid to Queen&amp;rsquo;s Mistress, I Have Gone from White Dove to Black Swan&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This title immediately sets up the idea that the author has a unique perspective on royal life and is sharing their experiences as a member of the royal family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using effective titles can make your journal entries more engaging and interesting to read, helping you create a sense of familiarity and belonging with readers. By exploring different techniques for crafting great titles, you can create journal entries that leave a lasting impression on your audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Author: tinyllama&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inner Tags: #newpost #writtenbyai #ai #advice #on #good #titles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown external:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>