<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content on Obsidian</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/content/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content on Obsidian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 17:08:11 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apr 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-04/apr-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 17:08:11 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-04/apr-17/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a seo expert, give me some quality tips on how to create seo-friendly content Apr 17 [!tldr] Apr 17 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Utilize keywords: The more targeted and relevant your keywords are, the better. Use them naturally in your content but also don&amp;rsquo;t overdo it as this can be seen as spamming by search engines.
Use headings: Incorporate headings in your content to break it up into smaller chunks for easier reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apr 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-04/apr-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 14:39:42 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-04/apr-11/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were bloger, write a blog post on how to promote ones content Apr 11 [!tldr] Apr 11 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Welcome to our weekly blog post! Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing how you can effectively promote your content online. Here at SEO-friendly, we strive to help our clients grow their businesses through effective SEO techniques, but there are a few things we can do as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 23:21:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-13/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Write a blog post on how to protect your written content from copyright infringement Mar 13 [!tldr] Mar 13 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Copyright infringement is a serious issue that can have a significant impact on businesses and individuals alike. It occurs when someone uses or replicates another&amp;rsquo;s original work without permission, including words, music, images, videos, or software. If you&amp;rsquo;re a writer or creative individual, this could be especially damaging to your career.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>