<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>than on Obsidian</title>
    <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/tags/than/</link>
    <description>Recent content in than on Obsidian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:36:34 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/tags/than/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mar 17</title>
      <link>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:36:34 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obsidiannotes.artefaktas.eu/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;prompt-act-as-if-you-were-a-writer-write-a-blog-post-on-how-to-entertain-oneself-for-less-than-10-euros&#34;&gt;Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a blog post on how to entertain oneself for less than 10 euros&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;mar-17&#34;&gt;Mar 17&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!tldr] Mar 17
TLDR
Text is too short to sumarize&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a busy professional juggling multiple tasks and deadlines, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to get caught up in the daily grind. Sometimes, all it takes is a few quarters at the coffee shop or a quick walk around the block to recharge your batteries. But what if you could entertain yourself for less than 10 euros?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure, there are countless ways to do this. You could take up a new hobby like knitting, cooking, or playing music. Or simply relax and enjoy a movie, listen to an album or read a book. Here are some suggestions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the local library - Many libraries offer free access to books on a wide range of topics. If you&amp;rsquo;re feeling adventurous, try borrowing a classic novel or discovering new authors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attend a play, music show or comedy event at your local venue. You could even create your own play or musical with friends by putting together a playlist on Spotify.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grab a quick bite to eat at a nearby café, cafe bar or food truck. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s coffee and pastries for breakfast or grilled cheese sandwiches for lunch, there are plenty of affordable options to satisfy your hunger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the local museum - Some museums offer discounted admission days or even free admission on certain weekends. You could also take a guided tour or just roam around and explore the exhibits at your own pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit an indoor playground or kids&amp;rsquo; park. Most indoor parks are designed to accommodate children of all ages, so you can choose one that suits your needs. Many offer discounted tickets or free admission during weekday hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy a picnic at the local park - Many parks have tables and chairs available for visitors to enjoy their food and drinks while enjoying nature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a walk in a nearby park, trail or forest. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a peaceful stroll or an adventurous hike, there are plenty of options around you to explore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a cooking class - From learning how to make homemade pasta to attending a French baking course, cooking classes offer a fun and educational way to spend less than 10 euros.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteer at a local charity or non-profit organization. While you&amp;rsquo;re there, you could also pick up some new skills through volunteering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go on a spontaneous adventure - Sometimes the best things to do are those that happen when you least expect them. Take a chance and explore an unfamiliar neighborhood or visit a place that seems out of character for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With these suggestions, you can easily spend less than 10 euros and enjoy some much-needed relaxation time in your busy schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Author: tinyllama&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inner Tags: #newpost #writtenbyai #entertainment #for #less #than #ten #euros&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internal links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;External links if exist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown external:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>