<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>On on Obsidian</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/on/</link>
    <description>Recent content in On on Obsidian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 11:43:05 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/on/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apr 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-04/apr-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 11:43:05 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-04/apr-3/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a tutorial on how to create an awesome blog post Apr 3 [!tldr] Apr 3 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Dear Reader,
Welcome to our blog! We&amp;rsquo;re excited to share with you our latest post that will help you understand how to create an outstanding blog post. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or a seasoned writer, this guide will provide you with the knowledge and skills you need to succeed in creating engaging content for your readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 30</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 13:03:11 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-30/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Write a short guideline on how to cope with stress Mar 30 [!tldr] Mar 30 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Coping with stress is an important skill for maintaining mental well-being and overall health. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to help you manage stress effectively:
Identify the sources of stress in your life. This may involve keeping a journal to track when you experience high levels of stress and what events or situations seem to trigger it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 28</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:15:07 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-28/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Write a blog post on how to stay creative Mar 28 [!tldr] Mar 28 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, staying creative has become increasingly important. With all the distractions and interruptions, it can be challenging to find time for creativity in our busy schedules. But let me share with you a few tips on how to stay creative!
Take breaks: Sometimes we get so caught up in work or life that we forget to take breaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 27</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 11:47:04 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-27/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a writer, write a blog post on how to create good titles for your journal entries Mar 27 [!tldr] Mar 27 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
Title: The Art of Creating Captivating Journal Entries
As a writer, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to know that great titles are crucial for attracting and retaining readers. A well-crafted title not only captures the reader&amp;rsquo;s attention but also sets up expectations about what they can expect from your journal entries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:14:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-26/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a developer, write a post on how to stay productive by using nowadays technologies Mar 26 [!tldr] Mar 26 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
As a busy programmer and project manager, I know how important it is to be efficient and focused to get things done. Here are some nowaday technologies that can help you stay productive:
Productivity software: There are several productivity software tools out there, such as Trello, Asana, Monday, and Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:16:37 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/journal/2024-03/mar-25/</guid>
      <description>Prompt: Act as if you were a professional web developer, write a blog post explaining why it is a good idea to use serverless architecture Mar 25 [!tldr] Mar 25 TLDR Text is too short to sumarize
In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced technology world, where even small businesses are embracing the cloud and adopting the latest trends, the concept of serverless architecture has gained immense popularity. Let me explain why it is a good idea to use serverless architecture for your web development projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>